Please check that out as well!
My parents told me to read this book, so I did.
And when I saw it, I was hooked.
I was hooked.
Waka Yasumori and Dine Kitami, right?
I don't know about those two.
Karen sends me a very long message every year.
Karen sends me long messages every year.
"I can't ride my bike.
There's a manga I'm not allowed to read.
Until I'm 20.
After that, I'm banned.
What do you think?
Nighttime and idols
Hi there, I'm Stardust, and I grew up in the middle class.
I have a wonderful guest for you today.
Hi!
I'm Pearl Kichise from Tohoku Inoue. Nice to meet you.
Yes, I am. I am Ms. Kichise from Inoue Tohoku. I would like to ask you a favor.
Today is different from usual, isn't it? Mr. Kettle.
Oh, yes. Did you pass by?
Let me see. Mr. Yakan, the first generation was a bit difficult today.
There was a second generation, but the second generation was also having difficulties,
I am the third generation Yakan-kun, and I would like to serve you today as the third Yakan-kun.
I look forward to working with you.
I am the third Yakan-kun.
Speaking of Mr. Kichise, he just celebrated his birthday on June 22.
Yay!
How old are you?
I turned 20 years old.
It's a memorable 20th year.
Yes, it is. I have that memorable 20 years old,Yes, I am. There was that memorable 20th birthday,
On June 25th, we had a cue ball at the Sporty Five O West in Shibuya, Tokyo,
Yay!
How was it?
It was a lot of fun. It was a great success.
It's not what I would call it if I said so myself.
You are indeed a master, aren't you?
But really, everyone came to the venue just for me,
I was so happy that everyone came to the venue for me and celebrated for me,
I almost cried at the end.
What was the event like?
I sang and sang and sang.
I think I sang about 15 songs.
I guess fans sent you congratulatory messages on your instagram,
Did you receive any messages from the members?
Yes, I did. I get a very long and lengthy message from Karin every year.
She always sends me a very long message on the anniversary of my joining the group.
I look forward to those messages, and I was happy to receive it this time as well.
Also, I noticed that the members post on their Instagram stories,
I wondered when they took these videos.
So there are things that you don't know about.
That's right. That's why I was surprised, but I was okay with it.
That's fine. That part is fine.
It's totally fine.
I'm a member.
As long as they don't look like this.
We are a happy family, too.
On the other hand, do you send messages to your child members on their birthdays?
Of course I do.
You know, I am not a member,
I'm not a member, but when I send a message to Lil'a, who is a member of the Batension Girls Club, I give her a LINE stamp,
I also give LINE stamps.I will also give you a LINE stamp.
Then I came back the other day...the LINE stamp was from Lil'a.
As a gift.
As a present.
I sent her the stamp, gave it to her as a gift, and sent her a message,
That's right.
She's so cute.
So, they are taking it in.
In a way, you are expanding your business into new areas.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
Okay, bye-bye.
This was sent to you courtesy of Hiyama-san.
Thank you, everyone. Rabbit.